{"_id":{"$oid":"5dc14423c44f050017ee784b"},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1572946979326"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1572946979326"},"formValue":{"name":"Sebastian","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Sebastian Nitu","location":"Erlangen","date":"2019-12-04 to 2019-12-06","questions":[{"question":"Content","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Architectural overview","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Components of the GUI","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Creating your first EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Adding behavior to your EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with templates","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding more functionality using widget features","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Creating a scrollable list with dynamic content","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Enhancing your EB GUIDE model with animations","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding conditional behavior","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling go-back functionality with history states","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling pop-ups with dynamic state machines","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with multiple state machines","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Dealing with focus and key input features","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Adding support for multiple languages","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with EB GUIDE Speech","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Working with 3D objects","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"}]},{"question":"Which important topic did you miss?","question_type":null,"answer":"Nothing","subQuestions":[]},{"question":"Exercises","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Content","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Practical use","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Comprehensibility","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"}]},{"question":"Did this training meet your expectations?","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Structuring","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Time management","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Overall rating","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"}]},{"question":"General Conditions (optional)","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Organization","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Location","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Catering","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"}]},{"question":"Own remarks","question_type":null,"answer":"Nothing","subQuestions":[]}]}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f167ba9c6a9be00177ee295"},"formValue":{"name":"Likhitha","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Sonal Patil,Sahana Mahadevappa","location":"EB India (Online)","date":"2020-04-27 to 2020-06-16","questions":[{"question":"Content","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Architectural overview","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Components of the GUI","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Creating your first EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding behavior to your EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with templates","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding more functionality using widget features","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Creating a scrollable list with dynamic content","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Enhancing your EB GUIDE model with animations","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Adding conditional behavior","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling go-back functionality with history states","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling pop-ups with dynamic state machines","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with multiple state machines","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Dealing with focus and key input features","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Adding support for multiple languages","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Working with EB GUIDE Speech","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Working with 3D objects","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"}]},{"question":"Which important topic did you miss?","question_type":null,"answer":"No","subQuestions":[]},{"question":"Exercises","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Content","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Practical use","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Comprehensibility","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"3"}]},{"question":"Did this training meet your expectations?","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Structuring","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Time management","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Overall rating","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"}]},{"question":"General Conditions (optional)","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Organization","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Location","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"2"},{"sub_ques":"Catering","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"2"}]},{"question":"Own remarks","question_type":null,"answer":"Overall informative.","subQuestions":[]}]},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1595308969970"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1595308969970"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f17e2011c8cc900174d58a8"},"formValue":{"name":"","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Sonal Patil,Sahana Mahadevappa","location":"EB India (Online)","date":"2020-04-27 to 2020-06-16","questions":[{"question":"Content","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Architectural overview","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Components of the GUI","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Creating your first EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding behavior to your EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with templates","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding more functionality using widget features","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Creating a scrollable list with dynamic content","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Enhancing your EB GUIDE model with animations","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding conditional behavior","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling go-back functionality with history states","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling pop-ups with dynamic state machines","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with multiple state machines","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Dealing with focus and key input features","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding support for multiple languages","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with EB GUIDE Speech","content_rating":"2","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with 3D objects","content_rating":"2","presentation_rating":"4"}]},{"question":"Which important topic did you miss?","question_type":null,"answer":"Speech, 3D objects","subQuestions":[]},{"question":"Exercises","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Content","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Practical use","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Comprehensibility","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"}]},{"question":"Did this training meet your expectations?","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Structuring","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Time management","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Overall rating","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"}]},{"question":"General Conditions (optional)","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Organization","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Location","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Catering","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"}]},{"question":"Own remarks","question_type":null,"answer":"Good","subQuestions":[]}]},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1595400705233"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1595400705233"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f18fa867aebdf001712c89e"},"formValue":{"name":"","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Sonal Patil,Sahana Mahadevappa","location":"EB India (Online)","date":"2020-04-27 to 2020-06-16","questions":[{"question":"Content","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Architectural overview","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Components of the GUI","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Creating your first EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Adding behavior to your EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Working with templates","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Adding more functionality using widget features","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Creating a scrollable list with dynamic content","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Enhancing your EB GUIDE model with animations","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding conditional behavior","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling go-back functionality with history states","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling pop-ups with dynamic state machines","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with multiple state machines","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Dealing with focus and key input features","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding support for multiple languages","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with EB GUIDE Speech","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with 3D objects","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"}]},{"question":"Which important topic did you miss?","question_type":null,"answer":"3D objects and Animations","subQuestions":[]},{"question":"Exercises","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Content","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Practical use","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Comprehensibility","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"}]},{"question":"Did this training meet your expectations?","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Structuring","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Time management","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Overall rating","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"}]},{"question":"General Conditions (optional)","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Organization","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Location","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"1"},{"sub_ques":"Catering","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"1"}]},{"question":"Own remarks","question_type":null,"answer":"Overall Good.","subQuestions":[]}]},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1595472518304"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1595472518304"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f228ce0d257450017b4ef2b"},"formValue":{"name":"Vasu Gupta","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Sonal Patil,Sahana Mahadevappa","location":"EB India (Online)","date":"2020-04-27 to 2020-06-16","questions":[{"question":"Content","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Architectural overview","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Components of the GUI","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Creating your first EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding behavior to your EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with templates","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Adding more functionality using widget features","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Creating a scrollable list with dynamic content","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Enhancing your EB GUIDE model with animations","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Adding conditional behavior","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling go-back functionality with history states","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling pop-ups with dynamic state machines","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Working with multiple state machines","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Dealing with focus and key input features","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding support for multiple languages","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with EB GUIDE Speech","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Working with 3D objects","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"}]},{"question":"Which important topic did you miss?","question_type":null,"answer":"Modeling go-back functionality with history states","subQuestions":[]},{"question":"Exercises","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Content","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Practical use","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Comprehensibility","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"3"}]},{"question":"Did this training meet your expectations?","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Structuring","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Time management","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Overall rating","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"}]},{"question":"General Conditions (optional)","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Organization","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Location","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Catering","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"3"}]},{"question":"Own remarks","question_type":null,"answer":"Training sessions are really good and time management was also planned very well.","subQuestions":[]}]},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596099808729"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596099808729"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f228eddd257450017b4ef2c"},"formValue":{"name":"Tejas B V","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Sonal Patil,Sahana Mahadevappa","location":"EB India (Online)","date":"2020-04-27 to 2020-06-16","questions":[{"question":"Content","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Architectural overview","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Components of the GUI","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Creating your first EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Adding behavior to your EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Working with templates","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Adding more functionality using widget features","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Creating a scrollable list with dynamic content","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Enhancing your EB GUIDE model with animations","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding conditional behavior","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling go-back functionality with history states","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling pop-ups with dynamic state machines","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Working with multiple state machines","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Dealing with focus and key input features","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Adding support for multiple languages","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Working with EB GUIDE Speech","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Working with 3D objects","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"3"}]},{"question":"Which important topic did you miss?","question_type":null,"answer":"3D animations","subQuestions":[]},{"question":"Exercises","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Content","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Practical use","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Comprehensibility","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"}]},{"question":"Did this training meet your expectations?","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Structuring","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Time management","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Overall rating","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"}]},{"question":"General Conditions (optional)","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Organization","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Location","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Catering","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"}]},{"question":"Own remarks","question_type":null,"answer":"Training was helpful and presentation was really good.","subQuestions":[]}]},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596100317067"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596100317067"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5f2293bed257450017b4ef2d"},"formValue":{"name":"Nitheesh","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Sonal Patil,Sahana Mahadevappa","location":"EB India (Online)","date":"2020-04-27 to 2020-06-16","questions":[{"question":"Content","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Architectural overview","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Components of the GUI","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Creating your first EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Adding behavior to your EB GUIDE model","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Working with templates","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding more functionality using widget features","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Creating a scrollable list with dynamic content","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Enhancing your EB GUIDE model with animations","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Adding conditional behavior","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling go-back functionality with history states","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Modeling pop-ups with dynamic state machines","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Working with multiple state machines","content_rating":"5","presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Dealing with focus and key input features","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Adding support for multiple languages","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with EB GUIDE Speech","content_rating":"3","presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Working with 3D objects","content_rating":"4","presentation_rating":"4"}]},{"question":"Which important topic did you miss?","question_type":null,"answer":"None","subQuestions":[]},{"question":"Exercises","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Content","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Practical use","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Comprehensibility","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"}]},{"question":"Did this training meet your expectations?","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Structuring","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Time management","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Overall rating","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"}]},{"question":"General Conditions (optional)","question_type":"rating","answer":null,"subQuestions":[{"sub_ques":"Organization","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Location","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"},{"sub_ques":"Catering","content_rating":null,"presentation_rating":"5"}]},{"question":"Own remarks","question_type":null,"answer":"Awesome initiative to know EB's own UI product being HMI dev. Giving more insight on developing our own applications.","subQuestions":[]}]},"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1596101566032"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1596101566032"}}
